<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[/dev/blog/caseyhadden]]></title>
  <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-02-02T14:34:59-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://caseyhadden.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Casey Hadden]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maturity and the Message]]></title>
    <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/02/02/maturity-and-the-message/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-02T12:29:06-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/02/02/maturity-and-the-message</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One evening we arrived home with stars visible in the night sky.
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orion_(constellation)">Orion</a> was just peeking
over the tree line. As we&rsquo;d recently attended an event at <a href="http://www.moreheadplanetarium.org/">Morehead
Planetarium</a> where they mentioned this
particular constellation, I took the opportunity to point it out to the family.</p>

<p>The youngest, 2 years old, couldn&rsquo;t make sense of my description. He believed I&rsquo;d seen a
lion and was understandably scared. The middle child, 4 years old, dutifully fulfilled her
role as an older sister and trying to explain it. She kept repeating, &ldquo;No, it&rsquo;s not
a&#8217;rion, it&rsquo;s a&#8217;rion.&rdquo; Translation: It&rsquo;s not a lion, it&rsquo;s Orion. The oldest, 7 years old,
understood it all. She understood what I was communicating as well as where her siblings
were falling down.</p>

<ul>
<li>How often does the audience lack the maturity to understand our message?</li>
<li>How often is the our delivery of the message too immature to understand?</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deer in the Dawn Light]]></title>
    <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/01/23/deer-in-the-dawn-light/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-23T15:03:16-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/01/23/deer-in-the-dawn-light</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As I left my house this morning, a group of deer appeared in an open area of
the yard. As my headlights illuminated the herd, they moved. For a brief
instant, I saw them frolicking. Just as quickly, that perception changed. I saw
them as they were, panicked, racing around to avoid a car that was no danger to
them. Two deer stood at the rear, safely watching the scene.</p>

<p>How often do we appear to do one thing (frolicking), while actually doing
something else (panicking), when we really should do a third (standing
still)?</p>

<p>How often do we look busy, accomplishing a task, when we’re really racing,
trying to make something demonstrable, but we should be quiet, contemplative
about what our real objective is?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
