<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[/dev/blog/caseyhadden]]></title>
  <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/"/>
  <updated>2018-09-09T09:45:38-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://caseyhadden.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Casey Hadden]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Duck Tales]]></title>
    <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2016/01/29/duck-tales/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-29T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2016/01/29/duck-tales</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Meet Jasper.</p>

<p><img src="http://caseyhadden.com/images/jasper.png"></p>

<p>Jasper lives at my house with 9 of his friends. However, Jasper has a problem - there are
only 6 hens versus 4 drakes. It&rsquo;s unfortunate, but that ratio doesn&rsquo;t work. You want a
ratio of 3:1 or more to keep everyone happy and healthy. There are several options to deal
with this and we choose to list Jasper on
<a href="http://raleigh.craigslist.org/grd/5395004180.html">craigslist</a>. Now, you can&rsquo;t list the
duck for free. That has a single predictable outcome; he&rsquo;s dinner. We attach a nominal fee
and wait with little expectation of finding a taker.</p>

<p>Over two weeks later, we get our first and still only response:</p>

<pre><code>Hi! I was wondering if I could rent your duck for a day. I am willing to pay the full
price for purchase and return him at the end of the day. We will treat him with the
utmost care and follow any guidelines you provide us. We would like to use him to
surprise our friend. He will be constantly monitored. Please let me know if you would be
willing to rent him.
</code></pre>

<p>My initial thoughts are rambling and numerous. Is this for real? Are they going to
mistakenly wire me thousands of dollars to rent a duck in a scam? Is this person&rsquo;s friend
going to have a transcendental experience like <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t5jw3T3Jy70">Kristen Bell</a>?
How do you come the conclusion that you might find a duck to rent on craigslist?</p>

<p>There is a bit that stands out the most, <strong>He will be constantly monitored</strong>. It is a little
threatening out of context. A farmer once shared with us that the only way to keep goats
inside their fence was razor wire and towers with snipers. I&rsquo;m now imagining that scene with
Jasper.  Let&rsquo;s add an ankle monitor to the razor wire and snipers. Just for added safety,
you see.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s only later that I realize the potential here. Unfortunately,
<a href="http://rentaduck.com">rentaduck.com</a> is already owned, though seemingly inactive. Perhaps
if the initial VC round closes well, we could pry the domain away from its current owner.
I don&rsquo;t want to count anything before the hatch, but perhaps <a href="http://www.dw.com/en/germanys-latest-craze-slug-eating-ducks-for-rent/a-2739835">there&rsquo;s more</a>
than just the surprise-a-friend angle here.</p>

<p>To make a long story end, we won&rsquo;t be renting Jasper. But if anyone needs a Cayuga drake
to add to their flock, I might just have one for you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maturity and the Message]]></title>
    <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/02/02/maturity-and-the-message/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-02T12:29:06-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/02/02/maturity-and-the-message</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One evening we arrived home with stars visible in the night sky.
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orion_(constellation)">Orion</a> was just peeking
over the tree line. We&rsquo;d recently attended an event at
<a href="http://www.moreheadplanetarium.org/">Morehead Planetarium</a> where they mentioned this
particular constellation, and I took the opportunity to point it out to the family.</p>

<p>The youngest, 2 years old, couldn&rsquo;t make sense of my description. He believed I&rsquo;d seen a
lion and was understandably scared. The middle child, 4 years old, dutifully fulfilled her
role as an older sister and trying to explain it. She kept repeating, &ldquo;No, it&rsquo;s not
a&#8217;rion, it&rsquo;s a&#8217;rion.&rdquo; Translation: It&rsquo;s not a lion, it&rsquo;s Orion. The oldest, 7 years old,
understood it all. She understood what I was communicating as well as where her siblings
were falling down.</p>

<ul>
<li>How often does the audience lack the maturity to understand our message?</li>
<li>How often is the our delivery of the message too immature to understand?</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deer in the Dawn Light]]></title>
    <link href="http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/01/23/deer-in-the-dawn-light/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-23T15:03:16-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://caseyhadden.com/blog/2015/01/23/deer-in-the-dawn-light</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As I left my house this morning, a group of deer appeared in an open area of
the yard. As my headlights illuminated the herd, they moved. For a brief
instant, I saw them frolicking. Just as quickly, that perception changed. I saw
them as they were, panicked, racing around to avoid a car that was no danger to
them. Two deer stood at the rear, safely watching the scene.</p>

<p>How often do we appear to do one thing (frolicking), while actually doing
something else (panicking), when we really should do a third (standing
still)?</p>

<p>How often do we look busy, accomplishing a task, when we’re really racing,
trying to make something demonstrable, but we should be quiet, contemplative
about what our real objective is?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
